medicisinfo.com 2014-06-25

# Valeant Privacy Policy

Valeant respects the privacy of the visitors to our Web sites. We will only collect personally identifiable information such as names, addresses, and the like, only when voluntarily provided to us at this Web site. We, or companies we hire will only use this information to comply with your request for information or as otherwise disclosed to you at the location where you submit the information. We may from time to time refer to that information in an effort to understand your needs and better serve you by improving our products and or services. We may also use that information to contact you. We will not sell or transfer your personally identified information to any third party unless disclosed to you when you submit your information.

Your IP address may be logged so that we can track your session on this site and thus serve you better. When analyzing our traffic, we also look at where our visitors have been referred from (the last URL you visited before visiting this Web site), your domain, and what browser and operating system you are using.

This site may deposit information commonly referred to as "cookies" in a visitor's computer. A cookie is a token that a server gives to your browser when you access a Web site. They store many types of data, and help provide additional functionality to our Web site. Cookies do not collect personally identifiable information.

If you provide personally identifiable information to this site, we may combine such information with other actively collected information unless we specify otherwise at the point of collection. We may disclose personally identifiable information you provide via this site to other Valeant affiliates worldwide that agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy and use it for the same purposes. We also may disclose personally identifiable information you provide via this site to third parties that are not Valeant affiliates, but only:

(i) to contractors we use to support our business (such as fulfillment services, technical support, delivery services, and financial institutions), in which case we will require such third parties to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy and use it for the same purposes;

(ii) in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the product or business of this site to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy and use it for the same purposes; or

(iii) to respond to law enforcement.

You have the right to ensure that your personal data is always up-to-date. In some countries you have the legal right to require us to correct or delete your personal data. In addition, you can always tell us to stop contacting you. If you wish to contact us regarding our use of your personal data, please e-mail us at pharmcs@valeant.com. If you contact us, please note the name of the website where you provided the information, as well as the specific information you would like us to correct, update or delete. Your requests will be dealt with in a prompt and proper manner. Requests to delete personal data will be subject to any applicable legal and ethical reporting or document filing or retention obligations imposed on us.

The Valeant Web site is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of thirteen. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we know to be under the age of thirteen.

This privacy policy was last updated August 31, 2004. Please refer to this page from time to time to review updates to this policy.
